<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="..\config8\suzuki.xsl" ?><!DOCTYPE suzuki [<!ENTITY % sdatacharaents SYSTEM "..\config8\sdatacharaents.txt">%sdatacharaents;]><suzuki><manual>
<section sectnbr = "2D">
<servcat sctnbr = "02" scnbr = "04">
<configtype typenbr = "0">
<servinfotype sitcode = "6">
<servinfo servinfosgmlid = "AENAP70A2406004" svcinfotypenbr = "08" svcinfoqualnbr = "03" page = "2" supplyoff = "1" modify = "0">
<title>
Wheel Balance Inspection and Adjustment
</title>
<attention1>
<ptxt>
Stones in the tread of a tire may injure the operator when the wheel is spun for balancing. Remove all stones from the tire tread before starting the operation. This is also important to obtain a good balancing result.
</ptxt>
</attention1>
<ptxt>
Before starting operation of wheel balance inspection and adjustment, remove all mud and other deposits from the rim inside area. Also check that tire is free of damage.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Follow recommendations of wheel balancing equipment&apos;s manufacturer.
</ptxt>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70A2406004001">
<title>
Off-Vehicle Balancing
</title>
<ptxt>
Electronic off-vehicle wheel balancers are easy to use. Most of them provide dynamic, two-plane balancing with high accuracy (usually capable of detecting imbalance of within 1/8 ounce), although they cannot be used for correcting brake disc imbalance unlike with on-vehicle wheel balancers.
</ptxt>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70A2406004002">
<title>
On-Vehicle Balancing
</title>
<ptxt>
On-vehicle balancing methods vary with equipment and tool manufacturers. Be sure to follow each manufacturer’s instructions during balancing operation.
</ptxt>
<attention1>
<ptxt>
If a drive wheel is spun at a speed higher than 55 km/h (35 mph) in speedometer reading, there is a risk of tire disintegration and differential system failure, eventually resulting in serious personal injuries and/or extensive vehicle damage including differential failure. This limit must be respected because the speedometer indicates only one-half of the actual wheel speed when one drive wheel is spinning while the other drive wheel is stopped. Be sure to limit the spinning speed of a drive wheel to 55 km/h (35 mph) in speedometer reading.
</ptxt>
</attention1>
<attention2>
<ptxt>
Using on-vehicle balancing method with ignition “ON” may set DTC of ESP<sup>®</sup> even when system is in good condition.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Never set ignition “ON” while spinning wheel.
</ptxt>
</attention2>
</servinfosub>
</servinfo>
</servinfotype>
</configtype>
</servcat>
</section></manual></suzuki>
