<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="..\config8\suzuki.xsl" ?><!DOCTYPE suzuki [<!ENTITY % sdatacharaents SYSTEM "..\config8\sdatacharaents.txt">%sdatacharaents;]><suzuki><manual>
<section sectnbr = "1J">
<servcat sctnbr = "01" scnbr = "10">
<configtype typenbr = "0">
<servinfotype sitcode = "6">
<servinfo servinfosgmlid = "AENAP70A1A06001" svcinfotypenbr = "08" svcinfoqualnbr = "03" page = "2" supplyoff = "1" modify = "1">
<title>
Jump-Starting in Case of Emergency
</title>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70A1A06001001">
<title>
With Booster Battery
</title>
<attention2>
<ptxt>
Do not push or tow it to start. This may cause damage to emission control system and/or to other components.
</ptxt>
</attention2>
<ptxt>
Both booster and discharged battery should be treated carefully when using jumper cables. Follow the procedure outlined as follows, being careful not to cause sparks.
</ptxt>
<attention1>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Departure from these conditions and procedure described below could result in serious personal injury (particularly to eyes) or property damage by battery explosion, battery acid or electrical burns.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Remove rings, watches and other jewelry. Be sure to wear approved eye protection.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention1>
<attention2>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Departure from these conditions and procedure described below could result in damage to electronic components of either vehicle.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Be careful not to allow metal tools or jumper cables to contact positive (+) battery terminal and any other metal on vehicle, because a short circuit could occur.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention2>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Place gear shift lever in “Neutral”. 
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Apply parking brake.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Set ignition “OFF”.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Turn off lights and all other electrical loads.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
For battery with cell caps, check electrolyte level. If it is below low level line, add distilled water.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Attach end of one jumper cable to positive (+) terminal of booster battery and other end of the same cable to positive (+) terminal of discharged battery (Use 12-volt battery only to jump-start engine).
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Attach one end of the remaining negative (–) cable to negative (–) terminal of booster battery, and other end to solid engine ground (such as exhaust manifold) at least 45 cm (18 in.) away from battery of vehicle being started.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Start engine of vehicle with booster battery and turn off its electrical loads. Then try to start engine of vehicle with discharged battery.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Disconnect jumper cables in exact reverse order.
</ptxt>
</s1>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70A1A06001002">
<title>
With Charging Equipment
</title>
<attention2>
<ptxt>
When jump-starting engine with charging equipment, be sure that equipment is for 12-volt and negative (–) ground system. Do not use 24-volt charging equipment. Using such equipment can cause serious damage to electrical system or electronic parts.
</ptxt>
</attention2>
</servinfosub>
</servinfo>
</servinfotype>
</configtype>
</servcat>
</section></manual></suzuki>
