<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="..\config8\suzuki.xsl" ?><!DOCTYPE suzuki [<!ENTITY % sdatacharaents SYSTEM "..\config8\sdatacharaents.txt">%sdatacharaents;]><suzuki><manual>
<section sectnbr = "5C">
<servcat sctnbr = "05" scnbr = "03">
<configtype typenbr = "0">
<servinfotype sitcode = "6">
<servinfo servinfosgmlid = "AENAP70A5306007" svcinfotypenbr = "08" svcinfoqualnbr = "03" page = "2" supplyoff = "1" modify = "1">
<title>
Air Bleeding of Clutch System
</title>
<attention2>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Brake fluid (Clutch fluid) is extremely damaging to paint. If fluid should accidentally touch painted surface, immediately wipe fluid from paint and clean painted surface.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
When operating the clutch pedal for air bleeding, after releasing the clutch pedal, be sure to wait 1 second or more before depressing it again. Otherwise, the oil seal of operating cylinder will be damaged, resulting in oil leakage.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention2>
<ptxt>
Bleeding operation is necessary to remove air whenever it entered hydraulic clutch system.
</ptxt>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Fill master cylinder reservoir with brake fluid and keep at least one-half full of fluid during bleeding operation.
</ptxt>
<spec-sdm>
<sdm-title>
Clutch fluid
</sdm-title>
<sdm-part>
</sdm-part>
<sdm1>
<sdm-condition>
</sdm-condition>
<sdm-value>
Refer to reservoir cap
</sdm-value>
</sdm1>
</spec-sdm>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Remove bleeder plug cap. Attach a vinyl tube (1) to bleeder plug, and insert the other end into container (2).
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "IAP70A530004.jpg" width = "88.000mm" height = "41.381mm" ver = "01" gw = "146" gh = "101"/>
</figure>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Depress clutch pedal several times, and then while holding it depressed, loosen bleeder plug about one-third to one-half turn.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
When fluid pressure in cylinder is almost depleted, retighten bleeder plug.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Repeat this operation until there are no more air bubbles in hydraulic line.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
When bubbles stop, depress and hold clutch pedal, and tighten bleeder plug to specified torque.
</ptxt>
<torque>
<torqueitem id = "T5C003">
<t-part>
Clutch bleeder plug
</t-part>
<t-value1>
5.0
</t-value1>
<t-value2>
0.51
</t-value2>
<t-value3>
4.0
</t-value3>
</torqueitem>
</torque>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Attach bleeder plug cap.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
After completing bleeding operation, apply fluid pressure to pipe line and check for leakage.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Replenish master cylinder reservoir with fluid up to specified level.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Check clutch pedal for operation. If spongy condition is felt, repeat entire procedure of bleeding.
</ptxt>
</s1>
</servinfo>
</servinfotype>
</configtype>
</servcat>
</section></manual></suzuki>
