<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="..\config8\suzuki.xsl" ?><!DOCTYPE suzuki [<!ENTITY % sdatacharaents SYSTEM "..\config8\sdatacharaents.txt">%sdatacharaents;]><suzuki><manual>
<section sectnbr = "8B">
<servcat sctnbr = "08" scnbr = "02">
<configtype typenbr = "0">
<servinfotype sitcode = "6">
<servinfo servinfosgmlid = "AENAP70A8206031" svcinfotypenbr = "08" svcinfoqualnbr = "03" page = "2" supplyoff = "1" modify = "0">
<title>
Deployed Air Bag (Inflator) Module and Activated Seat Belt Pretensioner Disposal
</title>
<attention1>
<ptxt>
Failure to follow proper air bag (inflator) module and seat belt pretensioner disposal procedures can result in air bag deployment and pretensioner activation which may cause personal injury. Undeployed air bag (inflator) module and inactivated seat belt pretensioner must not be disposed of through normal refuse channels.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Undeployed air bag (inflator) module and inactivated seat belt pretensioner contains substances that can cause severe illness or personal injury if sealed container is damaged during disposal.
</ptxt>
</attention1>
<ptxt>
Deployed air bag (inflator) module and activated seat belt pretensioner can be disposed of in the same way which is used for disposal of any other parts. For their disposal, however, the following points should be noted.
</ptxt>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Immediately after deployment / activation air bag (inflator) module and seat belt pretensioner are hot. Wait for 30 minutes to cool them off before handling them.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Never apply water and oil etc. to deployed air bag (inflator) module and activated seat belt pretensioner to cool them off. Do not get on deployed air bag (inflator) module and activated seat belt pretensioner.
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "IYSQ01820095.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "50.323mm" ver = "01" gw = "152" gh = "126"/>
</figure>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
After air bag (inflator) module has been deployed, surface of air bag may contain a powdery residue. As with many service procedures, you should wear gloves and safety glasses.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
When disposing of deployed air bag (inflator) module and activated seat belt pretensioner, be sure to seal it in a vinyl bag.
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I3JA01820119.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "48.884mm" ver = "01" gw = "176" gh = "122"/>
</figure>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
When air bag (inflator) module and seat belt pretensioner have been deployed / activated inside vehicle leave them as installed to vehicle and scrap them.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Be sure to wash your hands with mild soap and water after handling them.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</servinfo>
</servinfotype>
</configtype>
</servcat>
</section></manual></suzuki>
