<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="..\config8\suzuki.xsl" ?><!DOCTYPE suzuki [<!ENTITY % sdatacharaents SYSTEM "..\config8\sdatacharaents.txt">%sdatacharaents;]><suzuki><manual>
<section sectnbr = "8A">
<servcat sctnbr = "08" scnbr = "01">
<configtype typenbr = "0">
<servinfotype sitcode = "0">
<servinfo servinfosgmlid = "AENCP70A8100001" svcinfotypenbr = "01" svcinfoqualnbr = "01" page = "2" supplyoff = "1" modify = "0">
<title>
Precautions for Service and Diagnosis of Seat Belt
</title>
<attention1>
<ptxt>
If replacing seat belt assembly is necessary, replace buckle and seat belt assembly together. This is essential to correct locking of tongue plate in buckle. For this reason, SUZUKI will supply spare buckle and seat belt assembly only as a set.
</ptxt>
</attention1>
<attention2>
<ptxt>
Do not reuse the seat belt pretensioner (retractor) that has activated. Replace them with new front seat belt assembly and buckle together as a set. For checking procedure of the activation, refer to 
<intxref refid = "AENCP70A8204051">Repair and Inspection Required after Accident</intxref>
.
</ptxt>
</attention2>
<ptxt>
Before servicing or replacing seat belt assembly, refer to the following precautionary items.
</ptxt>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Be sure to check if tongue plate and buckle are normal.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Keep sharp edges and damaging objects away from webbing.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Never bend or damage buckle and tongue plate.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Do not bleach or dye webbing. (Use only mild soap and lukewarm water to clean it.)
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
When installing a seat belt anchor bolt, first tighten it by hand to prevent cross-threading and then tighten to the specified torque.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Do not attempt any repair on seat belt assembly. If any fault is found, replace the seat belt as an assembly.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Keep belts dry and clean at all times.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Any defective part must be replaced with a new one.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Replace seat belt assembly whose webbing is cut or damaged.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Do not put anything into trim panel opening which seat belt webbing passes through.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
After an accident, whether the seat belt pretensioner has been activated or not, be sure to perform checks and repairs described on 
<intxref refid = "AENCP70A8204051">Repair and Inspection Required after Accident</intxref>
.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</servinfo>
</servinfotype>
</configtype>
</servcat>
</section></manual></suzuki>
