<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="..\config8\suzuki.xsl" ?><!DOCTYPE suzuki [<!ENTITY % sdatacharaents SYSTEM "..\config8\sdatacharaents.txt">%sdatacharaents;]><suzuki><manual>
<section sectnbr = "7">
<servcat sctnbr = "07" scnbr = "00">
<configtype typenbr = "0">
<servinfotype sitcode = "0">
<servinfo servinfosgmlid = "AENCP70A7000003" svcinfotypenbr = "01" svcinfoqualnbr = "01" supplyoff = "1" modify = "0">
<title>
Precautions for Servicing A/C System
</title>
<servinfosub id = "AENCP70A7000003001">
<title>
Handling HFC-134a (R-134a) Refrigerant and Specified Compressor Oil
</title>
<attention1>
<ptxt>
Handle the HFC-134a (R-134a) refrigerant with care as follows. If not, it may cause severe injury such as blindness and frostbite.
</ptxt>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Avoid contact with skin and eyes by wearing safety glasses and gloves. In case of contact with skin or eyes, get medical attention.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Keep away from fire. High temperature may cause toxic gas. Therefore, take care of much room ventilation.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
The temperature above 40 &#176;C (104 &#176;F) in the refrigerant container may cause explosion.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention1>
<attention2>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Do not expose bright metals to liquid refrigerant. Refrigerant combined with moisture is corrosive and tarnishes the surfaces of bright metals including chrome.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Do not discharge the refrigerant into atmosphere.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
The specified compressor oil for use with the refrigerant is highly hygroscopic.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Keep internal parts of the A/C system free from moisture and dirt. When disconnecting any line from the system, install a blind plug or cap to the fitting immediately.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
If pipes or hoses are replaced, replenish the system with the compressor oil to the specified amount from the compressor suction side referring to “Replenishing Compressor Oil” in 
<intxref refid = "AENCP70A7216001">Operation Procedure for Refrigerant Charge:Manual Type</intxref>
.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention2>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENCP70A7000003002">
<title>
Handling A/C Cycle Parts and Tooling
</title>
<attention2>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
When connecting hoses and pipes, apply a few drops of compressor oil to O-ring.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Replace O-rings with new ones whenever hoses, pipes and after parts are disconnected.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Route drain hose so as to avoid any contact of drainage with vehicle components.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
If pipes or hoses are replaced, replenish the system with the compressor oil to the specified amount from the compressor suction side referring to “Replenishing Compressor Oil” in 
<intxref refid = "AENCP70A7216001">Operation Procedure for Refrigerant Charge:Manual Type</intxref>
.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
When handling recovery and recycling equipment, be sure to follow the instruction manual for the equipment.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention2>
<attention3>
<ptxt>
Check local governmental regulations regarding working with refrigerator systems and its tooling.
</ptxt>
</attention3>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENCP70A7000003003">
<title>
Refrigerant Recovery
</title>
<ptxt>
When discharging refrigerant out of A/C system, always recover it using refrigerant recovery and recycling equipment because discharging HFC-134a (R-134a) refrigerant into atmosphere would cause adverse effect to environment. For the method, refer to “Recovery” in 
<intxref refid = "AENCP70A7216001">Operation Procedure for Refrigerant Charge:Manual Type</intxref>
.
</ptxt>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENCP70A7000003004">
<title>
Refrigerant Charge
</title>
<ptxt>
After performing compressor oil replenishment and evacuation, charge a proper amount of refrigerant to A/C system referring to “Charge” in 
<intxref refid = "AENCP70A7216001">Operation Procedure for Refrigerant Charge:Manual Type</intxref>
.
</ptxt>
</servinfosub>
</servinfo>
</servinfotype>
</configtype>
</servcat>
</section></manual></suzuki>
