<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="..\config8\suzuki.xsl" ?><!DOCTYPE suzuki [<!ENTITY % sdatacharaents SYSTEM "..\config8\sdatacharaents.txt">%sdatacharaents;]><suzuki><manual>
<section sectnbr = "8B">
<servcat sctnbr = "08" scnbr = "02">
<configtype typenbr = "0">
<servinfotype sitcode = "0">
<servinfo servinfosgmlid = "AENCP70A8200002" svcinfotypenbr = "01" svcinfoqualnbr = "01" page = "2" supplyoff = "1" modify = "1">
<title>
Precautions for Handling and Storage of Air Bag System Components
</title>
<attention1>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Never attempt to insert foreign matter such as flat-end screwdriver into the connector of air bag (inflator) module or seat belt pretensioner, as static electricity may cause accidental deployment.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Never attempt to disassemble the air bag (inflator) module. If any abnormality is found, replace it with new one as an assembly.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I9P60A820001.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "96.741mm" ver = "02" gw = "224" gh = "258"/>
</figure>
</attention1>
<attention2>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
If abnormality is found in a live (undeployed) air bag (inflator) module, be sure to deploy it before disposing it.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
When connecting connectors with a locking mechanism, be sure to lock them firmly. Improper locking may cause the connection detection pin to turn on the “AIR BAG” warning light.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
When conducting continuity check of wiring harness or removal check of connectors, be sure to use the special tool (A). Since terminals are chrome-plated to improve the electric conductivity, the direct contact of tester probe with terminals may peel off the plating causing a loss of reliability.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention2>
<servicetool>
<servicetoolitem id = "L8B001">
<s-part>
(A)
</s-part>
<s-number num = "09932-76010">
09932–76010
</s-number>
</servicetoolitem>
</servicetool>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I8T201821003.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "56.760mm" ver = "02" gw = "230" gh = "144"/>
</figure>
<servinfosub id = "AENCP70A8200002001">
<title>
SDM
</title>
<attention2>
<ptxt>
Never use SDM which has detected a condition that meets any of the deployment conditions. Refer to 
<intxref refid = "AENCP70A8204001">Air Bag Diagnostic System Check</intxref>
 when checking SDM.
</ptxt>
</attention2>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I9W10P821061.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "96.022mm" ver = "01" gw = "179" gh = "256"/>
</figure>
<item>
<ptxt>
If SDM installation part of floor is damaged, repair it completely before reinstallation.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
All SDM and mounting bracket fasteners must be carefully torqued and the arrow on SDM must be pointed toward the front of the vehicle to ensure proper operation of the air bag system.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENCP70A8200002002">
<title>
Live (Undeployed) Air Bag (Inflator) Module
</title>
<ptxt>
Special care is necessary when handling and storing live (undeployed) air bag (inflator) modules. Accidental deployment of air bag (inflator) module could throw itself or objects around it in the air.
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "IAW10A820002.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "102.136mm" ver = "01" gw = "208" gh = "273"/>
</figure>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENCP70A8200002003">
<title>
Live (Inactivated) Seat Belt Pretensioner
</title>
<attention1>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Never carry a seat belt pretensioner by holding the webbing.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
When placing a live seat belt pretensioner on a workbench or other surface, do not lay it with its exhaust hole side (1) facing down. Never place anything above the exhaust hole nor stack seat belt pretensioners.
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I9P60A820002.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "52.574mm" ver = "01" gw = "213" gh = "133"/>
</figure>
</item>
</list1>
<ptxt>
Otherwise, personal injury may result.
</ptxt>
</attention1>
<ptxt>
Special care is necessary when handling and storing a live (inactivated) pretensioner. Accidental activation of pretensioner will cause high pressure gas to blow off from the exhaust hole and retract the webbing (1) quickly into the retractor assembly (2). These actions may throw the pretensioner itself or objects around it in the air.
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I9P60A820003.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "49.837mm" ver = "01" gw = "198" gh = "125"/>
</figure>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENCP70A8200002004">
<title>
Deployed Air Bag (Inflator) Module and Activated Seat Belt Pretensioner
</title>
<ptxt>
Refer to 
<intxref refid = "AENCP70A8206027">Deployed Air Bag (Inflator) Module and Activated Seat Belt Pretensioner Disposal</intxref>
.
</ptxt>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENCP70A8200002005">
<title>
Air Bag Wire Harness and Connector
</title>
<ptxt>
Air bag wire harness includes in main harness (1), instrument panel harness (2) and floor harness (3). Air bag wire harness can be identified easily as the connector side wire harness is covered with a yellow protection tube or tape. Be careful when handling it.
</ptxt>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
If damaged harness, connector or terminal is found on an air bag wire harness, replace the harness.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
When installing the air bag wire harness, be careful so that it is not caught or does not interfere with other parts.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Make sure air bag system grounding point (4) is clean and ground terminal is securely fastened for optimum metal-to-metal contact. Poor grounding can cause intermittent problems that are difficult to diagnose.
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I9P60A820004.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "66.864mm" ver = "01" gw = "217" gh = "173"/>
</figure>
</item>
</list1>
</servinfosub>
</servinfo>
</servinfotype>
</configtype>
</servcat>
</section></manual></suzuki>
