<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="..\config8\suzuki.xsl" ?><!DOCTYPE suzuki [<!ENTITY % sdatacharaents SYSTEM "..\config8\sdatacharaents.txt">%sdatacharaents;]><suzuki><manual>
<section sectnbr = "2B">
<servcat sctnbr = "02" scnbr = "02">
<configtype typenbr = "0">
<servinfotype sitcode = "6">
<servinfo servinfosgmlid = "AENAP70B2206005" svcinfotypenbr = "08" svcinfoqualnbr = "03" page = "2" supplyoff = "1" modify = "0">
<title>
Front Strut Inspection
</title>
<ptxt>
<intxrefpoff refid = "AENAP70B2206003">Front Strut Assembly Removal and Installation</intxrefpoff>
</ptxt>
<attention1>
<ptxt>
Since high-pressure gas is sealed inside front strut (1), there is risk of personal injury if it is handled without observing the following precautions.
</ptxt>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Do not disassemble front strut.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Do not put front strut into fire.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Do not store front strut where it gets hot.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Before disposing of front strut, be sure to drill an approximately 3 mm (0.1 in.) diameter hole (2) in it at point indicated in the figure to let gas out of the cylinder together with oil. Be sure to wear eye shield when drilling hole because metal chips produced by drilling can injure your eyes although the gas itself is harmless.
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I9P60A220012.jpg" width = "88.000mm" height = "56.121mm" ver = "01" gw = "158" gh = "143"/>
</figure>
</item>
</list1>
</attention1>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Check each front strut for oil leakage, damage or deformation. If check result is not OK, replace front strut as an assembly, as it is not repairable.
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I9P60A220013.jpg" width = "88.000mm" height = "83.704mm" ver = "01" gw = "113" gh = "221"/>
</figure>
</item>
<c-change/>
<item>
<ptxt>
Inspect front strut function as follows. If check result is not OK, replace front strut as an assembly, because it cannot be disassembled.
</ptxt>
</item>
<list2 type = "ordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Check and adjust tire pressures as specified.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Bounce vehicle body up and down 3 or 4 times continuously by pushing front end of vehicle side body to check front strut.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Also, note how many times vehicle body rebounds to stop after force application.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Repeat the same procedure to the other front strut to confirm that both struts equally function.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
If conditions of front struts are in doubt, compare them with known-good vehicle or front strut.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list2>
</list1>
</servinfo>
</servinfotype>
</configtype>
</servcat>
</section></manual></suzuki>
