<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="..\config8\suzuki.xsl" ?><!DOCTYPE suzuki [<!ENTITY % sdatacharaents SYSTEM "..\config8\sdatacharaents.txt">%sdatacharaents;]><suzuki><manual>
<section sectnbr = "7B">
<servcat sctnbr = "07" scnbr = "02">
<configtype typenbr = "2">
<servinfotype sitcode = "6">
<servinfo servinfosgmlid = "AENAP70B7226001" svcinfotypenbr = "08" svcinfoqualnbr = "01" supplyoff = "1" modify = "0">
<title>
Operation Procedure for Refrigerant Charge
</title>
<attention1>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Handle the HFC-134a (R-134a) refrigerant with care as follows. If not, it may cause severe injury such as blindness and frostbite.
</ptxt>
</item>
<list2 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Avoid contact with skin and eyes by wearing safety glasses and gloves. In case of contact with skin or eyes, get medical attention.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Keep away from fire. High temperature may cause toxic gas. Therefore, take care of much room ventilation.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
The temperature above 40 °C (104 °F) in the refrigerant container may cause explosion.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list2>
</list1>
</attention1>
<attention2>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Do not expose bright metals to liquid refrigerant. Refrigerant combined with moisture is corrosive and tarnishes the surfaces of bright metals including chrome.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
The specified compressor oil for use with the refrigerant is highly hygroscopic. Keep internal parts of A/C system free from moisture and dirt. When disconnecting any line from the system, install a blind plug or cap to the fitting immediately.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Do not discharge the refrigerant into atmosphere.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
When handling recovery and recycling equipment, be sure to follow the instruction manual for the equipment.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention2>
<attention3>
<ptxt>
Check local governmental regulations regarding working with refrigerator systems and its tooling.
</ptxt>
</attention3>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "IAP70A721042.swf" width = "183.000mm" height = "72.524mm" ver = "01" gw = "376" gh = "189"/>
</figure>
<p-change/>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B7226001001" page = "2">
<title>
Recovery
</title>
<ptxt>
When discharging refrigerant out of A/C system, always recover it using refrigerant recovery and recycling equipment because discharging refrigerant HFC-134a (R-134a) into atmosphere would cause adverse effect to environment.
</ptxt>
<attention3>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
After recovering refrigerant from system, the amount of removed compressor oil must be measured to determine the amount of compressor oil for replenishment.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
When handling recovery and recycling equipment, be sure to follow the instruction manual for the equipment.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention3>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "IAP70A721011.jpg" width = "88.000mm" height = "78.096mm" ver = "03" gw = "227" gh = "205"/>
</figure>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B7226001002" page = "2">
<title>
Replenishing Compressor Oil
</title>
<ptxt>
It is necessary to replenish A/C compressor with compressor oil to specified amount from compressor suction side hole (1) before evacuating system and charging it with refrigerant.
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "IAP70A721010.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "46.146mm" ver = "03" gw = "119" gh = "114"/>
</figure>
<topic id = "AENAP70B7226001003">
<title>
When charging refrigerant only
</title>
<ptxt>
When charging refrigerant without replacing any component, replenish A/C compressor with compressor oil of the same amount measured when recovering refrigerant (if not measured, add 30 cm<sup>3</sup> (30 ml, 1.01 US.oz, 1.06 Imp.oz) of oil).
</ptxt>
</topic>
<topic id = "AENAP70B7226001004">
<title>
When replacing compressor
</title>
<attention2>
<ptxt>
Be sure to use specified compressor oil or an equivalent compressor oil.
</ptxt>
</attention2>
<ptxt>
Compressor oil is sealed in each new A/C compressor by the amount required for A/C system. Therefore, when using a new A/C compressor, drain the calculated amount of oil from it.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
<emph etype = "bold">
“C” = “A” – “B”
</emph>
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
<emph etype = "bold">
“C”: Amount of oil to be drained
</emph>
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
<emph etype = "bold">
“A”: Amount of oil in a new A/C compressor
</emph>
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
<emph etype = "bold">
“B”: Amount of oil in removed A/C compressor
</emph>
</ptxt>
<attention3>
<ptxt>
A/C compressor assembly supplied from factory is filled up with the following amount of oil.
</ptxt>
</attention3>
<materials>
<materialitem name = "MITSUBISHI S10X" id = "M7B201" uid = "1078878149">
<m-part>
</m-part>
<m-desc>
Compressor oil
</m-desc>
<m-number>
99000–99095–00A
</m-number>
<m-name>
MITSUBISHI S10X
</m-name>
</materialitem>
</materials>
<spec>
<title>
Amount of oil in A/C compressor
</title>
<ptxt>
40 – 60 cm<sup>3</sup> (40 – 60 ml, 3.05 – 3.71 US.oz, 3.17 – 3.87 Imp.oz)
</ptxt>
</spec>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I7V20A720017.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "66.382mm" ver = "01" gw = "182" gh = "172"/>
<callout>
<table frame = "all" colsep = "1" rowsep = "1">
<tgroup cols = "4" colsep = "1" rowsep = "1">
<colspec colnum = "1" colname = "1" colwidth = "0.315in"/>
<colspec colnum = "2" colname = "2" colwidth = "1.379in"/>
<colspec colnum = "3" colname = "3" colwidth = "0.315in"/>
<colspec colnum = "4" colname = "4" colwidth = "1.379in"/>
<tbody>
<row rowsep = "0">
<entry colname = "1" border-top = "1" border-bottom = "1" border-left = "1" border-right = "0" valign = "top" align = "right">
<ptxt>
1.
</ptxt>
</entry>
<entry colname = "2" border-top = "1" border-bottom = "1" border-left = "0" border-right = "1" valign = "top" align = "left">
<ptxt>
New A/C compressor
</ptxt>
</entry>
<entry colname = "3" border-top = "1" border-bottom = "1" border-left = "1" border-right = "0" valign = "top" align = "right">
<ptxt>
2.
</ptxt>
</entry>
<entry colname = "4" border-top = "1" border-bottom = "1" border-left = "0" border-right = "1" valign = "top" align = "left">
<ptxt>
Removed A/C compressor
</ptxt>
</entry>
</row>
</tbody>
</tgroup>
</table>
</callout>
</figure>
</topic>
<topic id = "AENAP70B7226001005">
<title>
When replacing other parts
</title>
<ptxt>
Replenish A/C compressor with the following amount of oil.
</ptxt>
<spec>
<title>
Amount of A/C compressor oil to be replenished
</title>
<ptxt>
A/C evaporator: 15 cm<sup>3</sup> (15 ml, 0.51 US.oz, 0.53 Imp.oz)
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Condenser: 10 cm<sup>3</sup> (10 ml, 0.34 US.oz, 0.35 Imp.oz)
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Hoses: 5 cm<sup>3</sup> (5 ml, 0.17 US.oz, 0.18 Imp.oz) each
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Pipes: 5 cm<sup>3</sup> (5 ml, 0.17 US.oz, 0.18 Imp.oz) each
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Desiccant: 10 cm<sup>3</sup> (10 ml, 0.34 US.oz, 0.35 Imp.oz)
</ptxt>
</spec>
</topic>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B7226001006" page = "2">
<title>
Evacuation
</title>
<attention2>
<ptxt>
Do not evacuate A/C system before recovering refrigerant.
</ptxt>
</attention2>
<attention3>
<ptxt>
If A/C system circuit is opened (exposed) to atmosphere, system must be evacuated using a vacuum pump. The A/C system should be fitted with manifold gauge set, and should be evacuated for approximately 15 minutes.
</ptxt>
</attention3>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Connect high pressure charging hose (1) and low pressure charging hose (2) of special tool (3) (manifold gauge set) as follows:
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
High pressure charging hose → High pressure charging valve (4) on discharge hose
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Low pressure charging hose → Low pressure charging valve (5) on suction pipe
</ptxt>
<servicetool>
<servicetoolitem id = "L7B201">
<s-part>
(A)
</s-part>
<s-number num = "09990-06020">
09990–06020
</s-number>
</servicetoolitem>
</servicetool>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Attach center charging hose (6) of manifold gauge set to vacuum pump (7).
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Operate vacuum pump, and then open discharge side valve (HI) (8) of manifold gauge set.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
If there is no blockage in the system, there will be an indication on high pressure gauge (9).
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
When this occurs, open the other side valve (LO) (10) of the gauge set.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Approximately 10 minutes later, low pressure gauge (11) should show a vacuum lower than –100 kPa (–1.0 kgf/cm<sup>2</sup>, –760 mmHg, –14.7 psi), indicating that no leakage exists.
</ptxt>
<attention3>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
If the system does not show a vacuum below –100 kPa (–1.0 kgf/cm<sup>2</sup>, –760 mmHg, –14.7 psi), close both valves, stop vacuum pump and watch change in reading of low pressure gauge.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Increase in gauge reading suggests of leakage. In this case, repair the system before continuing its evacuation.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
If the gauge shows a stable reading (suggesting no leakage), continue evacuation.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention3>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Evacuation should be carried out for a total of at least 15 minutes.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Continue evacuation until lower pressure gauge indicates a vacuum less than –100 kPa (–1.0 kgf/cm<sup>2</sup>, –760 mmHg, –14.7 psi), and then close both valves.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Stop vacuum pump. Disconnect center charging hose from pump inlet. Now, the system is ready for charging refrigerant.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "IAP70B722005.jpg" width = "88.000mm" height = "92.496mm" ver = "02" gw = "217" gh = "246"/>
</figure>
</servinfosub>
<c-change/>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B7226001007" page = "2">
<title>
Checking A/C System for Pressure Leaks
</title>
<ptxt>
After completing the evacuation, close manifold gauge high pressure valve and low pressure valve and wait for 10 minutes. Verify that low pressure gauge reading has not changed.
</ptxt>
<attention2>
<ptxt>
If the gauge reading changes closer to “0”, there is a leak somewhere. Inspect the tubing connections and make necessary corrections. Evacuate system again and make sure that there are no leaks.
</ptxt>
</attention2>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B7226001008" page = "2">
<title>
Charge
</title>
<attention2>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Because the sight glass is not used for this A/C system, do not perform any additional charge to the A/C system. To charge the system with proper amount of refrigerant, recover the refrigerant and evacuate the A/C system first. Then charge A/C system with proper amount of refrigerant.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Always charge the A/C system through the low pressure side after the initial charge is performed from the high pressure side with the engine stopped.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Never charge the A/C system through the high pressure side with engine running.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Do not charge the A/C system while A/C compressor is hot.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
When installing tap valve to refrigerant container to make a hole there through, carefully follow directions given by manufacturer.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
A pressure gauge should always be used before and during refrigerant charge.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
The refrigerant container should be emptied of refrigerant when discarding it.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
The refrigerant container should not be heated to 40 °C (104 °F) or over.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Refrigerant container should not be turned upside down during refrigerant charge. Doing so causes liquid refrigerant to enter A/C compressor, causing troubles, such as compression of liquid refrigerant.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention2>
<c-change/>
<attention3>
<ptxt>
The A/C system contains HFC-134a (R-134a).
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Described here is a method for charging the A/C system with refrigerant from the refrigerant service container.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
When charging the system with the refrigerant recovered using the refrigerant recycling equipment, follow the procedure described in the equipment manufacturer’s instruction manual.
</ptxt>
</attention3>
<ptxt>
Perform initial charge through high pressure side with the engine stopped.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Next, charge the system with refrigerant as follows from low pressure side with engine running.
</ptxt>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Check if hoses are routed properly after evacuating system.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Connect low charging hose (1) and high charging hose (2) of manifold gauge set (3) in position. Then, open refrigerant container valve (4) to purge charging line.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Open high pressure side valve (5) to charge system with refrigerant.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
After a while, open low pressure side valve (6) and close high pressure side valve.
</ptxt>
<attention1>
<ptxt>
Make sure that high pressure side valve is closed securely. Failure to do so may cause explosion of refrigerant container because high pressure refrigerant way flow back into the container.
</ptxt>
</attention1>
</s1>
<c-change/>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Start engine and keep engine speed at 1500 r/min, then operate A/C system.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Charge A/C system with vapor refrigerant. At this time, refrigerant container should be held upright.
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "IAP70A721014.jpg" width = "88.000mm" height = "91.625mm" ver = "03" gw = "217" gh = "243"/>
</figure>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
When refrigerant container (1) is emptied, use the following procedure to replace it with a new refrigerant container.
</ptxt>
<s2>
<ptxt>
Close low pressure valve.
</ptxt>
</s2>
<s2>
<ptxt>
Replace empty container with a refrigerant container which has been charged with refrigerant. When using refrigerant container tap valve (2), use the following procedure for replacement.
</ptxt>
<s3>
<ptxt>
Turn handle of tap valve counterclockwise to retract needle (3), then remove refrigerant container tap valve by loosening its plate nut (4).
</ptxt>
</s3>
<s3>
<ptxt>
Install refrigerant container tap valve to new refrigerant container.
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I2RH01720018.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "49.476mm" ver = "01" gw = "89" gh = "123"/>
</figure>
</s3>
</s2>
<s2>
<ptxt>
Purge any air from center charging hose.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
When using refrigerant container tap valve, use the following procedure to purge air.
</ptxt>
<s3>
<ptxt>
Fully tighten refrigerant container tap valve (1), and then loosen (open) plate nut (2) slightly.
</ptxt>
</s3>
<s3>
<ptxt>
Open low pressure side valve (3) of manifold gauge set (4) a little.
</ptxt>
</s3>
<s3>
<ptxt>
As soon as refrigerant comes out with a “hiss” through a clearance between refrigerant container and tap valve, tighten plate nut as well as low pressure side valve.
</ptxt>
</s3>
<s3>
<ptxt>
Turn handle of tap valve clockwise so that its needle is screwed into the new container to make a hole for refrigerant flow.
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I2RH01720019.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "61.414mm" ver = "01" gw = "118" gh = "157"/>
</figure>
</s3>
</s2>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
After the system has been charged with specified amount of refrigerant or when low pressure gauge (1) and high pressure gauge (2) have indicated the following specified values, close low pressure side valve (3) on manifold gauge set (4).
</ptxt>
<spec>
<title>
Specified amount of refrigerant
</title>
<ptxt>
370 ± 20 g (13.1 ± 0.7 oz)
</ptxt>
</spec>
<spec>
<title>
Low pressure side and high pressure side example
</title>
<table frame = "all" colsep = "1" rowsep = "1">
<tgroup cols = "2" colsep = "1" rowsep = "1">
<colspec colnum = "1" colname = "1" colwidth = "1.732in"/>
<colspec colnum = "2" colname = "2" colwidth = "1.732in"/>
<tbody>
<row rowsep = "1">
<entry namest = "1" nameend = "2" border-top = "1" border-bottom = "1" border-left = "1" border-right = "1">
<ptxt>
Gauges should read as follows when ambient temperature is 30 °C (86 °F).
</ptxt>
</entry>
</row>
<row rowsep = "1">
<entry colname = "1" border-top = "1" border-bottom = "1" border-left = "1" border-right = "1">
<ptxt>
Pressure
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
on high pressure gauge
</ptxt>
</entry>
<entry colname = "2" border-top = "1" border-bottom = "1" border-left = "1" border-right = "1">
<ptxt>
1,100 – 1,540 kPa
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
(11.0 – 15.4 kgf/cm<sup>2</sup>)
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
(160 – 223 psi)
</ptxt>
</entry>
</row>
<row rowsep = "0">
<entry colname = "1" border-top = "1" border-bottom = "1" border-left = "1" border-right = "1">
<ptxt>
Pressure
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
on low pressure gauge
</ptxt>
</entry>
<entry colname = "2" border-top = "1" border-bottom = "1" border-left = "1" border-right = "1">
<ptxt>
290 – 440 kPa
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
(2.9 – 4.4 kgf/cm<sup>2</sup>)
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
(42.1 – 63.8 psi)
</ptxt>
</entry>
</row>
</tbody>
</tgroup>
</table>
</spec>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "IAP70A721015.jpg" width = "88.000mm" height = "92.190mm" ver = "03" gw = "217" gh = "245"/>
</figure>
</s1>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B7226001009" page = "2">
<title>
Removal of Manifold Gauge Set
</title>
<attention1>
<ptxt>
Be careful not to get injured by refrigerant from high pressure side especially in your eyes and skin.
</ptxt>
</attention1>
<ptxt>
For A/C system charged with specified amount of refrigerant, remove manifold gauge set as follows:
</ptxt>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Close low pressure side valve of manifold gauge set. (High pressure side valve has already been closed during charging process.)
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Close refrigerant container valve.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Stop engine.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Using shop rag, remove charging hoses from charging valves. This operation must be performed quickly.
</ptxt>
</s1>
<s1>
<ptxt>
Put caps on charging valves.
</ptxt>
</s1>
</servinfosub>
<c-change/>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B7226001010" page = "2">
<title>
Check A/C System for Refrigerant Leaks
</title>
<ptxt>
Whenever a refrigerant leak is suspected in the system or any service operation has been performed which may result in malfunction of lines and connections, it is important to perform check for leaks.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Common sense should be used during refrigerant leak test, since the need and extent of any such test will, in general, depend upon the nature of a complaint and the type of a service performed on the system.
</ptxt>
<topic id = "AENAP70B7226001011">
<title>
Liquid leak detector
</title>
<attention1>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
To prevent explosions and fires, make sure that there are no flammables in the vicinity.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
When the refrigerant is exposed to fire, it turns into a poisonous gas (phosgene). Do not inhale this gas.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention1>
<ptxt>
There is a number of fittings and places throughout the A/C system where liquid leak detector solution may be used to pinpoint refrigerant leaks.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
By applying the solution to the area in question with a swab, bubbles will form within seconds if there is a leak.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
For connections in such confined areas, as those around A/C evaporator and condenser, electronic (refrigerant) leak detector is more practical for determining leaks.
</ptxt>
<servicetool>
<servicetoolitem id = "L7B202">
<s-part>
(A)
</s-part>
<s-number num = "09990-86012">
09990–86012
</s-number>
</servicetoolitem>
</servicetool>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I5RW0A721054.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "43.678mm" ver = "01" gw = "181" gh = "107"/>
</figure>
</topic>
</servinfosub>
</servinfo>
</servinfotype>
</configtype>
</servcat>
</section></manual></suzuki>
