<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="..\config8\suzuki.xsl" ?><!DOCTYPE suzuki [<!ENTITY % sdatacharaents SYSTEM "..\config8\sdatacharaents.txt">%sdatacharaents;]><suzuki><manual>
<section sectnbr = "0B">
<servcat sctnbr = "00" scnbr = "02">
<configtype typenbr = "0">
<servinfotype sitcode = "6">
<servinfo servinfosgmlid = "AENAP70B0206037" svcinfotypenbr = "08" svcinfoqualnbr = "03" page = "2" supplyoff = "1" modify = "0">
<title>
Final Inspection for Maintenance Service
</title>
<attention1>
<ptxt>
When carrying out road tests, select a safe place without people and running vehicles to prevent any accident.
</ptxt>
</attention1>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B0206037001">
<title>
Seats
</title>
<ptxt>
Check that each front seat slides smoothly and locks securely at any position. Also check that reclining mechanism of each front seat allows the seatback to be locked at any angle.
</ptxt>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B0206037002">
<title>
Seat Belts
</title>
<ptxt>
Inspect seat belt systems including webbing, buckles, latch plates, retractors and anchors for damage or wear.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Check that each seat belt locks securely. If “REPLACE BELT” label on seat belt is visible, replace belt.
</ptxt>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B0206037003">
<title>
Battery Electrolyte Level Check
</title>
<ptxt>
Check that the electrolyte level of every battery cell is between the upper and lower level lines on the case. If battery is equipped with built-in indicator, check battery condition by the indicator.
</ptxt>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B0206037004">
<title>
Accelerator Pedal Operation
</title>
<ptxt>
Check that accelerator pedal operates smoothly without getting caught by or interfering any other part.
</ptxt>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B0206037005">
<title>
Engine Start
</title>
<ptxt>
Check the engine starts readily.
</ptxt>
<attention1>
<ptxt>
Be sure to observe the following precautions to prevent personal injuries and property damages in the event of accidental movements of vehicle.
</ptxt>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Provide enough spaces around the vehicle.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Firmly apply both the parking brake and foot brakes.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Do not use the accelerator pedal.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Be ready to set ignition “OFF” when engine starts.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention1>
<ptxt>
On A/T vehicles, try to start the engine in each select lever position. The starting motor should crank only in “P” (Park) or “N” (Neutral) range.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
On manual transaxle vehicles, place the gearshift lever in “Neutral”, depress clutch pedal halfway and try to start. 
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Starting motor should crank only when clutch pedal is fully depressed.
</ptxt>
</servinfosub>
<c-change/>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B0206037006">
<title>
Exhaust System Check
</title>
<ptxt>
Check for leakage, cracks or loose supports.
</ptxt>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B0206037007">
<title>
Clutch (Manual Transaxle Model)
</title>
<ptxt>
Check for the following:
</ptxt>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Clutch is completely released when clutch pedal is depressed.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
No slipping clutch occurs when releasing pedal and accelerating.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Clutch itself is free from any abnormal conditions.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B0206037008">
<title>
Gearshift or Select Lever
</title>
<ptxt>
Check gear shift or select lever for smooth movement to all positions and for good and correct response of transaxle in any position.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
With A/T equipped vehicles, also check that shift indicator indicates position correctly according to select lever position.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
With A/T equipped vehicles, also check that vehicle is at complete stop when select lever is placed in “P” range and all brakes are released.
</ptxt>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B0206037009">
<title>
Brakes
</title>
<topic id = "AENAP70B0206037010">
<title>
Foot brakes
</title>
<ptxt>
Check the following:
</ptxt>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Brake pedal has proper travel.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Brakes work properly.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Brakes do not generate abnormal noise.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Vehicle does not pull to one side when brakes are applied.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Brakes do not drag.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</topic>
<c-change/>
<topic id = "AENAP70B0206037011">
<title>
Parking brake
</title>
<ptxt>
Check that lever stroke is proper.
</ptxt>
<attention1>
<ptxt>
Observe the following precautions when performing parking brake test on a slope.
</ptxt>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Make sure that no person and obstruction is in the way ahead.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Be prepared to apply foot brakes quickly in case of a vehicle movement.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention1>
<ptxt>
Check that parking brake is fully effective when the vehicle is stopped on a slope by pulling parking brake lever all the way.
</ptxt>
</topic>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B0206037012">
<title>
Steering
</title>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Check that steering wheel is not instable and has no abnormally large resistance to turn.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Check that vehicle does not wander or pull to one side.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B0206037013">
<title>
Engine
</title>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Check that speed changes responsively to accelerator positions.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Check that engine is free from abnormal noise and abnormal vibration.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B0206037014">
<title>
Body, Wheels and Power Train Components
</title>
<ptxt>
Check that body, wheels and power train components are free from any abnormal conditions such as abnormal noise and vibration.
</ptxt>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B0206037015">
<title>
Meters and Gauges
</title>
<ptxt>
Check that speedometer, odometer, fuel gauge, temperature gauge, etc. are operating accurately.
</ptxt>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B0206037016">
<title>
Lights
</title>
<ptxt>
Check that all lights operate properly.
</ptxt>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENAP70B0206037017">
<title>
Windshield Defroster
</title>
<ptxt>
Periodically check that air comes out from defroster outlet when operating heater or air conditioning.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Set mode control lever to defroster position and fan switch lever to highest position for this check.
</ptxt>
</servinfosub>
</servinfo>
</servinfotype>
</configtype>
</servcat>
</section></manual></suzuki>
