<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="..\config8\suzuki.xsl" ?><!DOCTYPE suzuki [<!ENTITY % sdatacharaents SYSTEM "..\config8\sdatacharaents.txt">%sdatacharaents;]><suzuki><manual>
<section sectnbr = "1F">
<servcat sctnbr = "01" scnbr = "06">
<configtype typenbr = "0">
<servinfotype sitcode = "0">
<servinfo servinfosgmlid = "AENBP70A1600001" svcinfotypenbr = "01" svcinfoqualnbr = "01" supplyoff = "1" modify = "0">
<title>
Precautions for Cooling System
</title>
<attention1>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
If the radiator cap is removed while the engine is hot and pressure is high, the inside coolant will instantaneously boil up and spew out. This could cause severe burns or could cause a fire if coolant is splashed over the hot engine and exhaust system components, as the coolant contains a flammable anti-freeze material.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Never check the coolant level or add coolant by removing the radiator cap. Instead, be sure to check the coolant level only on the coolant reservoir and, if necessary, add coolant to the reservoir.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Also, make sure that the engine coolant temperature is cold before removing any part of cooling system.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention1>
<attention2>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
If service operations are performed on the engine cooling system with the battery connected, there is a risk of injury by accidental movement of the radiator cooling fan or other electric components.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Be sure to disconnect the negative (–) cable at the battery terminal before performing any service operations on the engine cooling system.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
The radiator cooling fan can come on whenever the ignition is ON. This electric fan starts automatically anytime the ECT sensor senses a coolant temperature higher than a predetermined level even when the engine is not running.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
When the ignition is ON, be sure to keep hands, tools, clothing, and other items away from the radiator cooling fan and drive belt.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention2>
</servinfo>
</servinfotype>
</configtype>
</servcat>
</section></manual></suzuki>
