<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="..\config8\suzuki.xsl" ?><!DOCTYPE suzuki [<!ENTITY % sdatacharaents SYSTEM "..\config8\sdatacharaents.txt">%sdatacharaents;]><suzuki><manual>
<section sectnbr = "9D">
<servcat sctnbr = "09" scnbr = "04">
<configtype typenbr = "0">
<servinfotype sitcode = "1">
<servinfo servinfosgmlid = "AENBP70A9401002" svcinfotypenbr = "03" svcinfoqualnbr = "01" supplyoff = "1" modify = "0">
<title>
Headlight Washer System Description
</title>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
The headlight washer system consists of the headlight auto leveling and washer control module, headlight washer pump, headlight washer nozzle, headlight washer switch, windshield washer switch and lighting switch.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
The headlight washer system is controlled by the headlight auto leveling and washer control module.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
The headlight auto leveling and washer control module monitors conditions of the headlight washer switch, windshield washer pump, lighting switch and engine switch. 
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
It is possible to monitor conditions of the headlight washer switch and windshield washer switch using SUZUKI scan tool.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
<servinfosub id = "AENBP70A9401002001">
<title>
Headlight Washer Control
</title>
<ptxt>
The headlight washer control has two control systems, one is auto control in which the headlight washer pump is activated together with windshield washer pump, and the other is manual control in which the headlight washer pump is activated by ON signal of the headlight washer switch.
</ptxt>
<topic id = "AENBP70A9401002002">
<title>
Auto / Manual control
</title>
<ptxt>
When all of the following conditions are met, the headlight auto leveling and washer control module activates the headlight washer pump for specified time.
</ptxt>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Ignition: ON
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Headlights: ON
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Headlight washer pump: OFF
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Windshield washer pump: ON (auto control)
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Headlight washer switch: ON (manual control)
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
<attention3>
<ptxt>
In the auto control, the headlight washer pump is activated only one time. The headlight washer pump is reactivated under either of the following conditions.
</ptxt>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Headlights: OFF → ON
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Ignition: OFF → ON, headlights: ON
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention3>
</topic>
</servinfosub>
</servinfo>
</servinfotype>
</configtype>
</servcat>
</section></manual></suzuki>
