<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="..\config8\suzuki.xsl" ?><!DOCTYPE suzuki [<!ENTITY % sdatacharaents SYSTEM "..\config8\sdatacharaents.txt">%sdatacharaents;]><suzuki><manual>
<section sectnbr = "2D">
<servcat sctnbr = "02" scnbr = "04">
<configtype typenbr = "0">
<servinfotype sitcode = "1">
<servinfo servinfosgmlid = "AENBP70A2401001" svcinfotypenbr = "03" svcinfoqualnbr = "01" page = "2" supplyoff = "1" modify = "0">
<title>
Tire Description
</title>
<ptxt>
This vehicle is equipped with tubeless tires of the following specifications.
</ptxt>
<spec-sdm>
<sdm-title>
Tire specifications
</sdm-title>
<sdm1>
<sdm-condition>
</sdm-condition>
<sdm-value>
195/50 R16 84V, 195/45 R17 81W
</sdm-value>
</sdm1>
</spec-sdm>
<attention3>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Tire inflation pressure should be checked when tires are cool.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
The tire inflation pressure will change due to changes in atmospheric pressure and temperature as well as in temperature of tire itself when driving. It is important to check and adjust the tire pressures when the tires are cold. Tires that appear to be at the specified pressure when checked after driving (when the tires are warm) will have pressure below the specification when the tires cool down. Also, tires that are inflated to the specified pressure in a warm garage may have pressure below the specification when the vehicle is driven outside in very cold temperature. If the tire pressure is adjusted in a place warmer than the outside, add 1 psi to the recommended cold tire inflation pressure for every 5.6 °C (42 °F) increase in the temperature of the adjustment place compared to the outside temperature.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Specified tire inflation pressure is indicated on the tire placard or in the vehicle’s owner’s manual.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention3>
<ptxt>
The tires are of a tubeless type. The tires are designed to operate satisfactorily with loads up to the full rated load capacity when inflated to the recommended inflation pressure.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Correct tire pressures and driving habits have an important influence on tire life. Hard cornering, excessively rapid acceleration, and unnecessary hard braking increase tire wear.
</ptxt>
</servinfo>
</servinfotype>
</configtype>
</servcat>
</section></manual></suzuki>
