<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="..\config8\suzuki.xsl" ?><!DOCTYPE suzuki [<!ENTITY % sdatacharaents SYSTEM "..\config8\sdatacharaents.txt">%sdatacharaents;]><suzuki><manual>
<section sectnbr = "2D">
<servcat sctnbr = "02" scnbr = "04">
<configtype typenbr = "0">
<servinfotype sitcode = "6">
<servinfo servinfosgmlid = "AENBP70A2406006" svcinfotypenbr = "08" svcinfoqualnbr = "01" page = "2" supplyoff = "1" modify = "0">
<title>
Tire Mounting and Dismounting
</title>
<attention1>
<ptxt>
Failure to take proper precautions when inflating a tire can result in severe personal injury.
</ptxt>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Do not stand over a tire being inflated. The tire’s bead may break if it snaps over the rim’s safety hump, possibly causing personal injury.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Do not inflate the tire to a pressure exceeding the specified value. Over-inflation may cause the bead to break, causing personal injury.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention1>
<attention2>
<ptxt>
Failure to use proper procedures when mounting and dismounting tires can result in improper mounting or damage to the tires and/or tire pressure sensors.
</ptxt>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Be sure to clean the tire bead seating surfaces on the rims with a wire brush or coarse steel wool to remove lubricants, old rubber and light rust.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Before mounting or dismounting a tire, be sure to lubricate the beads with an approved tire lubricant.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
After mounting a tire, first inflate it to 330 kPa (47.9 psi) so that its beads are completely seated. Then adjust the pressure to the correct value specified on the “Tire Placard”.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
If the tire bead is not completely seated at the specified pressure, deflate the tire, lubricate the beads again and then re-inflate the tire.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Do not try to complete changing a tire using hand tools or tire irons alone. Doing so may damage tire beads and/or wheel rims.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Install valve caps on all valves to keep out dust and water.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention2>
</servinfo>
</servinfotype>
</configtype>
</servcat>
</section></manual></suzuki>
