<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="..\config8\suzuki.xsl" ?><!DOCTYPE suzuki [<!ENTITY % sdatacharaents SYSTEM "..\config8\sdatacharaents.txt">%sdatacharaents;]><suzuki><manual>
<section sectnbr = "8B">
<servcat sctnbr = "08" scnbr = "02">
<configtype typenbr = "0">
<servinfotype sitcode = "0">
<servinfo servinfosgmlid = "AENBP70A8200002" svcinfotypenbr = "01" svcinfoqualnbr = "01" page = "2" supplyoff = "1" modify = "1">
<title>
Precautions for Handling and Storage of Air Bag System Components
</title>
<attention1>
<ptxt>
Measuring the resistance of any air bag (inflator) module (driver, passenger, side or curtain module) or any seat belt pretensioner (driver or passenger pretensioner) with a tester is dangerous, as the electric current from the tester may trigger the air bag or pretensioner.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Never attempt to measure the resistance of an air bag (inflator) module or seat belt pretensioner.
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I9P60A820001.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "96.741mm" ver = "02" gw = "224" gh = "258"/>
</figure>
</attention1>
<ptxt>
When checking each wiring harness, use special tool (A) referring to 
<intxref refid = "AENBP70A8208001">Use of Special Tools</intxref>
.
</ptxt>
<servicetool>
<servicetoolitem id = "L8B001">
<s-part>
(A)
</s-part>
<s-number num = "09932-76010">
09932–76010
</s-number>
</servicetoolitem>
</servicetool>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I8T201821003.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "56.760mm" ver = "02" gw = "230" gh = "144"/>
</figure>
<servinfosub id = "AENBP70A8200002001">
<title>
SDM
</title>
<attention1>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
If the SDM is not rigidly attached to the vehicle, it could accidentally cause the air bags to deploy when the air bag system is powered, possibly causing personal injury.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Always make sure that the SDM is rigidly attached to the vehicle before supplying power to the air bag system.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
The SDM that has been involved in an accident severe enough to cause deployment of air bags is not guaranteed to provide its original performance.
</ptxt>
<ptxt>
Never use an SDM that has been involved in an air bag deployment accident. Refer to 
<intxref refid = "AENBP70A8204001">Air Bag Diagnostic System Check</intxref>
 for the SDM check procedure.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</attention1>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Never attempt disassembly of SDM
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
When storing SDM, select a place where neither high temperature nor high humidity is anticipated and oil, water and dust are kept off.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I9W10P821061.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "96.022mm" ver = "01" gw = "179" gh = "256"/>
</figure>
<item>
<ptxt>
If SDM has been dropped, replace it with a new one.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
If SDM installation part of floor is damaged, repair it completely before reinstallation.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
All SDM and mounting bracket fasteners must be carefully torqued and the arrow on SDM must be pointed toward the front of the vehicle to ensure proper operation of the air bag system.
</ptxt>
</item>
</list1>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENBP70A8200002002">
<title>
Live (Undeployed) Air Bag (Inflator) Module
</title>
<ptxt>
Special care is necessary when handling and storing live (undeployed) air bag (inflator) modules. Accidental deployment of air bag (inflator) module could throw itself or objects around it in the air.
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "IAW10A820002.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "102.136mm" ver = "01" gw = "208" gh = "273"/>
</figure>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENBP70A8200002003">
<title>
Live (Inactivated) Seat Belt Pretensioner
</title>
<attention1>
<ptxt>
Failure to take proper precautions when handling and storing a live (non-activated) seat belt pretensioner can result in personal injury due to accidental activation of the pretensioner.
</ptxt>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
Handle or store a live seat belt pretensioner in a place with an ambient temperature below 65 &#176;C (149 &#176;F), without high humidity and away from electric noise sources.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Never carry a live seat belt pretensioner by holding the belt webbing.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
When placing a live seat belt pretensioner on a workbench or other flat surface, make sure that the pretensioner’s exhaust hole (1) side faces upward.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Do not put anything on the exhaust hole (1) side of a live seat belt pretensioner. Also avoid placing one live seat belt pretensioner on top of another.
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I9P60A820002.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "52.574mm" ver = "01" gw = "213" gh = "133"/>
</figure>
</item>
</list1>
</attention1>
<ptxt>
Special care is necessary when handling and storing a live (inactivated) pretensioner. Accidental activation of pretensioner will cause high pressure gas to blow off from the exhaust hole and retract the webbing (1) quickly into the retractor assembly (2). These actions may throw the pretensioner itself or objects around it in the air.
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "I9P60A820003.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "49.837mm" ver = "01" gw = "198" gh = "125"/>
</figure>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENBP70A8200002004">
<title>
Deployed Air Bag (Inflator) Module and Activated Seat Belt Pretensioner
</title>
<ptxt>
Refer to 
<intxref refid = "AENBP70A8206031">Deployed Air Bag (Inflator) Module and Activated Seat Belt Pretensioner Disposal</intxref>
.
</ptxt>
</servinfosub>
<servinfosub id = "AENBP70A8200002005">
<title>
Air Bag Wire Harness and Connector
</title>
<ptxt>
Air bag wire harness includes in main harness (1), instrument panel harness (2) and floor harness (3). Air bag wire harness can be identified easily as the connector side wire harness is covered with a yellow protection tube or tape. Be careful when handling it.
</ptxt>
<list1 type = "unordered">
<item>
<ptxt>
If damaged harness, connector or terminal is found on an air bag wire harness, replace the harness.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
When installing the air bag wire harness, be careful so that it is not caught or does not interfere with other parts.
</ptxt>
</item>
<item>
<ptxt>
Make sure air bag system grounding point (4) is clean and ground terminal is securely fastened for optimum metal-to-metal contact. Poor grounding can cause intermittent problems that are difficult to diagnose.
</ptxt>
<figure>
<graphic graphicname = "IBP60B820001.swf" width = "88.000mm" height = "66.864mm" ver = "01" gw = "217" gh = "173"/>
</figure>
</item>
</list1>
</servinfosub>
</servinfo>
</servinfotype>
</configtype>
</servcat>
</section></manual></suzuki>
